{
  "apikey": "%PUT-YOUR-API-KEY-HERE%",
  "description": "This is simple calibration data used for testing purposes. Do not use it in production environment!",
  "copyright": "Copyright (C) 2238 by BanAN Technologies Inc.",
  "test-data": [
    {
      "question": "82 + 28",
      "answer": 110
    },
    {
      "question": "89 + 63",
      "answer": 152
    },
    {
      "question": "74 + 88",
      "answer": 162
    },
    {
      "question": "100 + 54",
      "answer": 154
    },
    {
      "question": "100 + 91",
      "answer": 191
    },
    {
      "question": "66 + 81",
      "answer": 147
    },
    {
      "question": "95 + 38",
      "answer": 133
    },
    {
      "question": "72 + 66",
      "answer": 138
    },
    {
      "question": "79 + 44",
      "answer": 123
    },
    {
      "question": "63 + 48",
      "answer": 111
    },
    {
      "question": "46 + 88",
      "answer": 134
    },
    {
      "question": "57 + 45",
      "answer": 102
    },
    {
      "question": "18 + 83",
      "answer": 101
    },
    {
      "question": "98 + 71",
      "answer": 169
    },
    {
      "question": "62 + 41",
      "answer": 103
    },
    {
      "question": "78 + 77",
      "answer": 155
    },
    {
      "question": "41 + 99",
      "answer": 140
    },
    {
      "question": "23 + 80",
      "answer": 103
    },
    {
      "question": "67 + 67",
      "answer": 134
    },
    {
      "question": "88 + 99",
      "answer": 187
    },
    {
      "question": "62 + 95",
      "answer": 157
    },
    {
      "question": "9 + 3",
      "answer": 12
    },
    {
      "question": "84 + 82",
      "answer": 166
    },
    {
      "question": "90 + 88",
      "answer": 178
    },
    {
      "question": "66 + 2",
      "answer": 68
    },
    {
      "question": "14 + 49",
      "answer": 63
    },
    {
      "question": "12 + 20",
      "answer": 32
    },
    {
      "question": "43 + 85",
      "answer": 128
    },
    {
      "question": "28 + 24",
      "answer": 52
    },
    {
      "question": "20 + 10",
      "answer": 30
    },
    {
      "question": "67 + 5",
      "answer": 72
    },
    {
      "question": "19 + 22",
      "answer": 41
    },
    {
      "question": "85 + 76",
      "answer": 161
    },
    {
      "question": "70 + 61",
      "answer": 131
    },
    {
      "question": "75 + 80",
      "answer": 155
    },
    {
      "question": "33 + 98",
      "answer": 131
    },
    {
      "question": "63 + 43",
      "answer": 106
    },
    {
      "question": "45 + 88",
      "answer": 133
    },
    {
      "question": "18 + 91",
      "answer": 109
    },
    {
      "question": "71 + 52",
      "answer": 123
    },
    {
      "question": "83 + 51",
      "answer": 134
    },
    {
      "question": "94 + 29",
      "answer": 123
    },
    {
      "question": "6 + 41",
      "answer": 47
    },
    {
      "question": "28 + 27",
      "answer": 55
    },
    {
      "question": "6 + 73",
      "answer": 79
    },
    {
      "question": "60 + 98",
      "answer": 158
    },
    {
      "question": "37 + 3",
      "answer": 40
    },
    {
      "question": "92 + 93",
      "answer": 185
    },
    {
      "question": "2 + 100",
      "answer": 102
    },
    {
      "question": "94 + 44",
      "answer": 138
    },
    {
      "question": "63 + 99",
      "answer": 162
    },
    {
      "question": "6 + 51",
      "answer": 57
    },
    {
      "question": "90 + 77",
      "answer": 167
    },
    {
      "question": "1 + 16",
      "answer": 17
    },
    {
      "question": "79 + 92",
      "answer": 171
    },
    {
      "question": "58 + 17",
      "answer": 75
    },
    {
      "question": "29 + 79",
      "answer": 108
    },
    {
      "question": "56 + 8",
      "answer": 64
    },
    {
      "question": "8 + 7",
      "answer": 15
    },
    {
      "question": "20 + 36",
      "answer": 56
    },
    {
      "question": "100 + 36",
      "answer": 136
    },
    {
      "question": "67 + 30",
      "answer": 97
    },
    {
      "question": "6 + 6",
      "answer": 12
    },
    {
      "question": "21 + 71",
      "answer": 92
    },
    {
      "question": "76 + 51",
      "answer": 127
    },
    {
      "question": "77 + 50",
      "answer": 127
    },
    {
      "question": "14 + 100",
      "answer": 114
    },
    {
      "question": "14 + 30",
      "answer": 44
    },
    {
      "question": "27 + 20",
      "answer": 47
    },
    {
      "question": "56 + 53",
      "answer": 109
    },
    {
      "question": "86 + 80",
      "answer": 166
    },
    {
      "question": "56 + 80",
      "answer": 136
    },
    {
      "question": "25 + 25",
      "answer": 50
    },
    {
      "question": "66 + 38",
      "answer": 104
    },
    {
      "question": "76 + 52",
      "answer": 128
    },
    {
      "question": "74 + 98",
      "answer": 172
    },
    {
      "question": "83 + 30",
      "answer": 113
    },
    {
      "question": "73 + 29",
      "answer": 102
    },
    {
      "question": "31 + 45",
      "answer": 76
    },
    {
      "question": "50 + 46",
      "answer": 96
    },
    {
      "question": "54 + 18",
      "answer": 72
    },
    {
      "question": "79 + 30",
      "answer": 109
    },
    {
      "question": "72 + 34",
      "answer": 106
    },
    {
      "question": "42 + 83",
      "answer": 125
    },
    {
      "question": "32 + 90",
      "answer": 122
    },
    {
      "question": "91 + 59",
      "answer": 150
    },
    {
      "question": "69 + 25",
      "answer": 94
    },
    {
      "question": "22 + 35",
      "answer": 57
    },
    {
      "question": "29 + 63",
      "answer": 92
    },
    {
      "question": "78 + 23",
      "answer": 101
    },
    {
      "question": "51 + 84",
      "answer": 135
    },
    {
      "question": "91 + 82",
      "answer": 173
    },
    {
      "question": "43 + 79",
      "answer": 122
    },
    {
      "question": "19 + 94",
      "answer": 113
    },
    {
      "question": "65 + 54",
      "answer": 119
    },
    {
      "question": "72 + 92",
      "answer": 164
    },
    {
      "question": "9 + 63",
      "answer": 72
    },
    {
      "question": "21 + 47",
      "answer": 68
    },
    {
      "question": "96 + 1",
      "answer": 97
    },
    {
      "question": "83 + 13",
      "answer": 96
    }
  ],
  "chunk": {
    "number": 19,
    "total": 22,
    "size": 100,
    "range": {
      "from": 1800,
      "to": 1900
    }
  }
}